hey everybody welcome to this a1 english
listening practice video you can use
this video to practice your listening
and comprehension as i speak before we
start remember to download my listening
time podcast and become a listening time
member at patreon.com
listeningtime to receive my listening
practice seminars sound training videos
and bonus podcast episodes okay today
we're going to talk about working from
home this is a good topic because many
people work remotely nowadays
working remotely means you don't work in
an office you stay home and you use your
computer or other technology to work i
work from home and i think there are
positives and negatives to this
let's talk about them
first let's start with the positives if
you work from home you don't need to
commute to work you don't have to drive
to work in the morning or drive back
home in the evening this is great
because you don't have to worry about
traffic in the morning and in the
evening there are many cars on the road
because many people are commuting to and
from work
some people get stuck in this traffic
every day this is one of my favorite
things about working from home it saves
you a lot of time another thing is that
you can feel more relaxed when you work
from home
you can wear casual clothes you can take
breaks when you're tired and you can
work in any room i feel pretty
comfortable working from home it's not
too formal and i feel free
if you work in an office there are more
rules and it's less comfortable one
other positive about working from home
is being able to spend more time with
your family for example if you have a
break you can go in the other room and
spend time with your family when you
work at an office you don't have your
family with you so you can't do this i
love eating breakfast or lunch with my
family when i have breaks this is
probably the best part about working
from home i can spend a lot of time with
my family on weekdays and weekends okay
now let's talk about the negatives of
working from home one bad thing is that
it's easy to get distracted at home for
example if you have young children at
home with you it can be hard to focus on
your work children make noise and
interrupt you while you're working this
is normal so you have to learn to manage
these situations and stay focused on
your work another negative thing about
working from home is that sometimes you
don't know when to stop working when you
work at an office you stop working when
you leave the office you know exactly
when your work day is done however when
you work from home it can be hard to
know when to stop each day you don't
have your boss there to tell you when to
stop
one more negative thing about working
from home is not having contact with
other people in general it's important
to talk and interact with other people
if you work from home you only talk to
your co-workers on the computer or on
the phone this is okay but i think it's
also good to interact with people in
person it feels good to be around people
and to work with people so in general i
like working from home but it's not
perfect okay that's all for today leave
a comment and tell me if you like
working from home before you go remember
to download the listening time podcast
and if you want to improve your
listening become a member at patreon.com
listeningtime to receive my listening
practice seminars sound training videos
and bonus podcast episodes also
subscribe to the channel click on the
bell and follow us on instagram i'll see
you next time